let questions2 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "The most common device for interconnecting local area networks?",
        answer: "C. Switch",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Router",
            "B. Cloud",
            "C. Switch",
            "D. Firewall"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Helps direct messages as they travel across a network?",
        answer: "A. Router",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Router",
            "B. Cloud",
            "C. Switch",
            "D. Firewall"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "To send our instant message to its destination, the computer must be connected to a wired or wireless local network.",
        answer: "B. The Medium",
        options: 
        [
            "A. The Devices",
            "B. The Medium",
            "C. The Services",
            "D. The rules"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "This network can expand quickly to support new users and  applications without impacting the performance of the service being delivered to existing users.",
        answer: "A. Scalability",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Scalability",
            "B. Quality of Service",
            "C. Fault Tolerance",
            "D. Security"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "When a message is sent from source to destination,it must use a specific format or structure. ",
        answer: "D. Message Formatting",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Message Encoding",
            "B. Message Size",
            "C. Message Timing",
            "D. Message Formatting"
            
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which one of the following is a function of the Physcial Layer?",
        answer: "D. Encoding",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Presentation",
            "B. Physical",
            "C. Network",
            "D. Encoding"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Is the measure of the transfer of bits across the media over a given period of time? ",
        answer: "A. Throughput",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Throughput",
            "B. Goodput",
            "C. Session",
            "D. Data Link"
            
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "This cable consists of a copper conductor surrounded by a layer of flexible insulation?",
        answer: "B. Coaxial Cable",
        options: 
        [
            "A. UTP Cable",
            "B. Coaxial Cable",
            "C. Shielded Twisted-Pair Cable",
            "D. Fiber Media Cable"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a Fiber Media Connector?",
        answer: "D. Fiber MEdia Cable",
        options: 
        [ 
            "A. ST Connector",
            "B. SC Connector",
            "C. Multimode",
            "D. Fiber MEdia Cable"
            
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "A third measurement has been created to measure the transfer of usable data. That measure is known as?",
        answer: "B. Goodput",
        options: 
        [
            "A. Connector",
            "B. Goodput",
            "C. Session",
            "D. Throughput"
        ]
    }
];